Willem Gibson

10 St David Street Rippleside 3215 – 0490 471 225 – designsnoxic@gmail.com

Professional Summary

I will shortly be finishing Year 12 in September at Kardinia International College, with a strong focus on Information Technology (IT). In addition, I have 18 months of freelance experience in Graphic Design and Website Development working with various clients obtained through my own efforts. I believe I show great initiative as I have undertaken several short courses to further my skills in specific areas of interest.

Experience

Reading Cinemas

Cinema Attendant Dec 2020 – Present

Ivy Street

Work Experience – Graphic Design July 2021

Freelance Graphic Design

Self employed

Jun 2018 - Dec 2020

Previous clients:

- BTHoppers Installs
- Sunset Pier Cafe
- Andromedia

Freelance Web Development

Self employed

June 2018 - 2020

Previous Clients:

- Lucrative Apparel
- Aspex Graphics
- Soko Toys
- FURY Australia

Education

Kardinia International College – Year 12

Skills Graphic Design (18 months)

Web Development (18 months)

Programming (5 years)

Hobbies Guitar, Basketball, Movies, Collectables, Graphic Design,

Coding, Web Development.

Courses

Responsible Serving of Alcohol (RSA), Jan 2023 Complete C# Unity Developer, Udemy Jun, 2020

The Complete Python 3 Course, Udemy Jan, 2020

Logo Design Mastery: The Full Course, SkillShare Dec, 2019 Basic First Aid, Kardinia International College Apr, 2019 Graphic Design Bootcamp: Part 1 & 2, Udemy Jan, 2019

Links Personal portfolio https://behance.net/NoxicGraphics

Aspex Graphics Portfolio http://aspex.cloudaccess.host/

daniels-quickstart/

References Trent Downie, BT Hoppers Installs

0447 306 633, trent@bthoppers.com.au